[
    {
        "id": 422,
        "question": "Is the NULL value treated as 0?",
        "answers": {
            "answer_a": "True",
            "answer_b": "False",
            "answer_c": null,
            "answer_d": null,
            "answer_e": null,
            "answer_f": null
        },
        "tags": [
            {
                "name": "MySQL"
            }
        ],
        "category": "SQL",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "correct_answer": "answer_b"
    },
    {
        "id": 345,
        "question": "Which type of database management system represents relations using tables?",
        "answers": {
            "answer_a": "Network DBMS",
            "answer_b": "Hierachical DBMS",
            "answer_c": "Relational DBMS",
            "answer_d": "Object Oriented DBMS",
            "answer_e": null,
            "answer_f": null
        },
        "tags": [
            {
                "name": "MySQL"
            }
        ],
        "category": "SQL",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "correct_answer": "answer_c"
    },
    {
        "id": 392,
        "question": "Which among the following have the maximum available bytes?",
        "answers": {
            "answer_a": "Varchar",
            "answer_b": "Text Type",
            "answer_c": "Both Varchar And Char",
            "answer_d": "Char",
            "answer_e": null,
            "answer_f": null
        },
        "tags": [
            {
                "name": "MySQL"
            }
        ],
        "category": "SQL",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "correct_answer": "answer_b"
    },
    {
        "id": 214,
        "question": "What does the WHERE SQL operator does:",
        "answers": {
            "answer_a": "restricts the set of rows to the selection of those records for which the condition is true",
            "answer_b": "converts the value of a column or function to a different type",
            "answer_c": "changes the order of output rows",
            "answer_d": "eliminates all row repeats from the result set",
            "answer_e": null,
            "answer_f": null
        },
        "tags": [
            {
                "name": "MySQL"
            }
        ],
        "category": "SQL",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "correct_answer": "answer_a"
    }, {
        "id": 219,
        "question": "What does SQL stands for?",
        "answers": {
            "answer_a": "Structure query language",
            "answer_b": "Strong question language",
            "answer_c": "Structured question language",
            "answer_d": "Separate query language",
            "answer_e": null,
            "answer_f": null
        },
        "tags": [
            {
                "name": "MySQL"
            }
        ],
        "category": "SQL",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "correct_answer": "answer_a"
    }, {
        "id": 355,
        "question": "The command DROP SCHEMA `STUDENTS`; will delete the students database.",
        "answers": {
            "answer_a": "True",
            "answer_b": "False",
            "answer_c": null,
            "answer_d": null,
            "answer_e": null,
            "answer_f": null
        },
        "tags": [
            {
                "name": "MySQL"
            }
        ],
        "category": "SQL",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "correct_answer": "answer_a"
    }, {
        "id": 399,
        "question": "Which of the following is NOT supported by MySQL",
        "answers": {
            "answer_a": "Temporary (Hash) Tables",
            "answer_b": "Stored Procedures",
            "answer_c": "Regular Expression Matching",
            "answer_d": "Table Joining",
            "answer_e": null,
            "answer_f": null
        },
        "tags": [
            {
                "name": "MySQL"
            }
        ],
        "category": "SQL",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "correct_answer": "answer_b"
    }, {
        "id": 372,
        "question": "What will be the output of the SELECT CASE WHEN NULL = NULL THEN 'YES' ELSE 'NO' END",
        "answers": {
            "answer_a": "True",
            "answer_b": "False",
            "answer_c": "An Error will be generated",
            "answer_d": null,
            "answer_e": null,
            "answer_f": null
        },
        "tags": [
            {
                "name": "MySQL"
            }
        ],
        "category": "SQL",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "correct_answer": "answer_b"
    }, {
        "id": 206,
        "question": "SQL (Structured Query Language) is:",
        "answers": {
            "answer_a": "imperative programming language",
            "answer_b": "the language of structured queries",
            "answer_c": "the language of queries by pattern",
            "answer_d": "DBMS (DataBase Management System)",
            "answer_e": null,
            "answer_f": null
        },
        "tags": [
            {
                "name": "MySQL"
            }
        ],
        "category": "SQL",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "correct_answer": "answer_b"
    }, {
        "id": 425,
        "question": "TCL is used for _______?",
        "answers": {
            "answer_a": "Control access to data stored in a database",
            "answer_b": "Managing the changes made by DML statements",
            "answer_c": "Defining database schema",
            "answer_d": "None of the mentioned",
            "answer_e": null,
            "answer_f": null
        },
        "tags": [
            {
                "name": "MySQL"
            }
        ],
        "category": "SQL",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "correct_answer": "answer_b"
    }
]
